{
    "data": {
        "user" : {
            "7x1c8oJ72OQ3o7Z2CXrHlEO18eb2" : "{\"id\":\"7x1c8oJ72OQ3o7Z2CXrHlEO18eb2\",\"name\":\"New User\",\"email\":\"abcd@gmail.com\",\"coins\":100,\"character\":0,\"companion\":2000,\"ownedCollectibles\":{\"characters\":[0,1,1001],\"companions\":[2000,2001]}}",
            "8wbvmsoA2EhVwIwig69PlqwFQOC2" : "{\"id\":\"8wbvmsoA2EhVwIwig69PlqwFQOC2\",\"name\":\"New User\",\"email\":\"jp@e.com\",\"coins\":100,\"character\":0,\"companion\":2000,\"ownedCollectibles\":{\"characters\":[0,1,1001],\"companions\":[2000,2001]}}",
            "AuChCr76BcNuxKZRE6zevOSI1Sk1" : "{\"id\":\"AuChCr76BcNuxKZRE6zevOSI1Sk1\",\"name\":\"Test User 2\",\"email\":\"test123@test.com\",\"coins\":50,\"character\":1029,\"companion\":2007,\"ownedCollectibles\":{\"characters\":[0,1,1001,9,2,4,3,5,1029,1033],\"companions\":[2000,2001,2002,2007]}}",
            "GrNppxkmShfc69Ak8I6LXCYaxrV2" : "{\"id\":\"GrNppxkmShfc69Ak8I6LXCYaxrV2\",\"name\":\"kmkmk\",\"email\":\"sengwee_new@hotmail.com\",\"coins\":80,\"character\":4,\"companion\":2000,\"ownedCollectibles\":{\"characters\":[0,1,1001,22,4],\"companions\":[2000,2001]},\"username\":\"hi\"}",
            "Kaq55r9soLO8lhulNgRUomtXSot2" : "{\"id\":\"Kaq55r9soLO8lhulNgRUomtXSot2\",\"name\":\"New User\",\"email\":\"gmoaoainfasofsgmoaoainfasofsgmoaoainfasofsgmoaoainfasofsgmoaoainfasofsgmoaoainfasofsgmoaoainfasofs@gmail.com\",\"coins\":0,\"character\":11,\"companion\":2001,\"ownedCollectibles\":{\"characters\":[0,1,1001,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11],\"companions\":[2000,2001]}}",
            "TJvsK598L7cnkxryi9Il4O9ai642" : "{\"id\":\"TJvsK598L7cnkxryi9Il4O9ai642\",\"name\":\"New User\",\"email\":\"fkyou@e.com\",\"coins\":100,\"character\":0,\"companion\":2000,\"ownedCollectibles\":{\"characters\":[0,1,1001],\"companions\":[2000,2001]}}",
            "ikrg1b0STiP3NGjy9XG7FfSOeac2" : "{\"id\":\"ikrg1b0STiP3NGjy9XG7FfSOeac2\",\"name\":\"New User\",\"email\":\"test@gmail.com\",\"coins\":80,\"character\":2,\"companion\":2002,\"ownedCollectibles\":{\"characters\":[0,1,1001,2],\"companions\":[2000,2001,2002]},\"username\":\"Fad\"}",
            "rTD84RNkMNY6X27y214ZrjWLcvE3" : "{\"id\":\"rTD84RNkMNY6X27y214ZrjWLcvE3\",\"name\":\"New User\",\"email\":\"gerald.lau.95@gmail.com\",\"coins\":90,\"character\":1,\"companion\":2007,\"ownedCollectibles\":{\"characters\":[0,1,1001],\"companions\":[2000,2001,2007]}}"
          },
        "questions": {
            "lessons": {
                "Addition_&_Subtraction": {
                    "Level 1": {
                        "id": "Level 1",
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "id": 1,
                                "question": "7 + 9 = ?",
                                "options": [16, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 16
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 2,
                                "question": "3 + 8 = ?",
                                "options": [11, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 11
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 3,
                                "question": "5 + 10 = ?",
                                "options": [15, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 15
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 4,
                                "question": "6 + 4 = ?",
                                "options": [10, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 10
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 5,
                                "question": "14 - 6 = ?",
                                "options": [8, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 8
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 6,
                                "question": "10 - 7 = ?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 3
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 7,
                                "question": "3 - 1 = ?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 2
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 8,
                                "question": "9 - 4 = ?",
                                "options": [5, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 5
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    "Level 2": {
                        "id": "Level 2",
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "id": 1,
                                "question": "3 + ? = 10",
                                "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 7
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 2,
                                "question": "8 + ? = 15",
                                "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 7
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 3,
                                "question": "1 + ? = 6",
                                "options": [5, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 5
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 4,
                                "question": "3 + ? = 6",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 3
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 5,
                                "question": "? - 9 = 3",
                                "options": [12, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 12
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 6,
                                "question": "? - 6 = 5",
                                "options": [11, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 11
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 7,
                                "question": "8 - ? = 1",
                                "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 7
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 8,
                                "question": "4 - ? = 0",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 4
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    "Level 3": {
                        "id": "Level 3",
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "id": 1,
                                "question": "5 is more than 3 by _?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 2
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 2,
                                "question": "2 more than 4 is _?",
                                "options": [6, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 6
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 3,
                                "question": "3 is more than 1 by_?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 2
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 4,
                                "question": "8 more than 8 is _?",
                                "options": [16, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 16
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 5,
                                "question": "8 is fewer than 9 by _?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 1
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 6,
                                "question": "4 fewer than 6 is _?",
                                "options": [10, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 10
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 7,
                                "question": "4 is fewer than 11 by_?",
                                "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 7
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 8,
                                "question": "3 fewer than 5 is _",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 2
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    "Level 4": {
                        "id": "Level 4",
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "id": 1,
                                "question": "45 + 52 = ?",
                                "options": [97, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 97
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 2,
                                "question": "53 + 16 = ?",
                                "options": [69, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 69
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 3,
                                "question": "31 + 57 = ?",
                                "options": [88, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 88
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 4,
                                "question": "25 + 52 = ?",
                                "options": [77, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 77
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 5,
                                "question": "76 - 22 = ?",
                                "options": [54, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 54
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 6,
                                "question": "56 - 23 = ?",
                                "options": [33, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 33
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 7,
                                "question": "63 - 22 = ?",
                                "options": [41, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 41
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 8,
                                "question": "54 - 33 = ?",
                                "options": [21, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 21
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                }
            },
            "assignments": {
                "Addition_&_Subtraction": {
                    "Level 1": {
                        "id": "Level 1",
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "id": 1,
                                "question": "7 + 9 = ?",
                                "options": [16, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 16
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 2,
                                "question": "3 + 8 = ?",
                                "options": [11, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 11
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 3,
                                "question": "5 + 10 = ?",
                                "options": [15, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 15
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 4,
                                "question": "6 + 4 = ?",
                                "options": [10, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 10
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 5,
                                "question": "14 - 6 = ?",
                                "options": [8, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 8
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 6,
                                "question": "10 - 7 = ?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 3
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 7,
                                "question": "3 - 1 = ?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 2
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 8,
                                "question": "9 - 4 = ?",
                                "options": [5, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 5
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    "Level 2": {
                        "id": "Level 2",
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "id": 1,
                                "question": "3 + ? = 10",
                                "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 7
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 2,
                                "question": "8 + ? = 15",
                                "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 7
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 3,
                                "question": "1 + ? = 6",
                                "options": [5, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 5
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 4,
                                "question": "3 + ? = 6",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 3
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 5,
                                "question": "? - 9 = 3",
                                "options": [12, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 12
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 6,
                                "question": "? - 6 = 5",
                                "options": [11, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 11
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 7,
                                "question": "8 - ? = 1",
                                "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 7
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 8,
                                "question": "4 - ? = 0",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 4
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    "Level 3": {
                        "id": "Level 3",
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "id": 1,
                                "question": "5 is more than 3 by _?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 2
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 2,
                                "question": "2 more than 4 is _?",
                                "options": [6, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 6
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 3,
                                "question": "3 is more than 1 by_?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 2
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 4,
                                "question": "8 more than 8 is _?",
                                "options": [16, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 16
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 5,
                                "question": "8 is fewer than 9 by _?",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 1
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 6,
                                "question": "4 fewer than 6 is _?",
                                "options": [10, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 10
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 7,
                                "question": "4 is fewer than 11 by_?",
                                "options": [7, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 7
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 8,
                                "question": "3 fewer than 5 is _",
                                "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 2
                            }
                        ]
                    },
                    "Level 4": {
                        "id": "Level 4",
                        "questions": [
                            {
                                "id": 1,
                                "question": "45 + 52 = ?",
                                "options": [97, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 97
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 2,
                                "question": "53 + 16 = ?",
                                "options": [69, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 69
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 3,
                                "question": "31 + 57 = ?",
                                "options": [88, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 88
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 4,
                                "question": "25 + 52 = ?",
                                "options": [77, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 77
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 5,
                                "question": "76 - 22 = ?",
                                "options": [54, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 54
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 6,
                                "question": "56 - 23 = ?",
                                "options": [33, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 33
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 7,
                                "question": "63 - 22 = ?",
                                "options": [41, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 41
                            },
                            {
                                "id": 8,
                                "question": "54 - 33 = ?",
                                "options": [21, 2, 3, 4],
                                "answer": 21
                            }
                        ]
                    }
                }
            },
            "challenge": {
                "Challenge 1": {
                    "id": "Challenge 1",
                    "creator_id": "1",
                    "title": "1",
                    "questions": [
                        {
                            "id": 1,
                            "question": "7 + 9 = ?",
                            "options": [16, 2, 3, 4],
                            "answer": 16
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 2,
                            "question": "3 + 8 = ?",
                            "options": [11, 2, 3, 4],
                            "answer": 11
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 3,
                            "question": "5 + 10 = ?",
                            "options": [15, 2, 3, 4],
                            "answer": 15
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 4,
                            "question": "6 + 4 = ?",
                            "options": [10, 2, 3, 4],
                            "answer": 10
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 5,
                            "question": "14 - 6 = ?",
                            "options": [8, 2, 3, 4],
                            "answer": 8
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 6,
                            "question": "10 - 7 = ?",
                            "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                            "answer": 3
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 7,
                            "question": "3 - 1 = ?",
                            "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
                            "answer": 2
                        },
                        {
                            "id": 8,
                            "question": "9 - 4 = ?",
                            "options": [5, 2, 3, 4],
                            "answer": 5
                        }
                    ]
                }
    
            }
        }
    }
}